so I've been working with Aaron uh and
Sammy these are my two uh two of my
bikini girls right now they actually
want to train for a powerlifting
competition so here's Aaron right now
deadlifting 155 that's a one rep max she
keeps very good position as you can see
um she Dees this with high hips but she
has good discipline not rounding that's
what's important so here's 165 she
doesn't quite get it but as you can see
keeps disciplin doesn't allow her to
round over and try it um here's Sammy
this is her first time squatting heavy
with me with a barbell and I was showing
her what her I wanted to film a video
and show her what her low back is doing
she's got buttwink um and she didn't
realize this cuz no one's ever filmed a
video now she has an incredibly strong
spine and and the strongest glutes I've
ever out of anyone I've ever trained so
I think that protects her cuz she
doesn't injure herself but I filmed this
to to show her how bad this is she needs
more hip flexion mobility and more ankle
Mobility which will be trying to get
over time but it could be anatomical
maybe there's no fixing it in which case
we'll have to think up Solutions okay
here's Aaron deadlifting 135 we wanted
to get a rep max uh repetition Max with
135 and I think she gets four or maybe
five um again she de us with high hips
which I'm fine with she keeps great
spinal position and um
has good discipline here she she gets it
halfway up there and doesn't allow her
form to to erode and drops it so I was
very happy with air in there uh here's
Sammy with 85 lbs again I got close to
show that buttwink it's it's crazy now
some trainers would modify and not let
her squat I wanted to do a heavy session
because this is my first time I trained
her last year uh and we did tons of we
did tons of hip thrusting she got up to
185lb hip thrust but we did CLE Bell
deadlifts and we did lever squats so she
never really did barbell squats with me
so I wanted to see what she could do and
she hasn't been doing any heavy lifting
lately except for some hip thrusting
okay here's Aaron this is 85
lbs uh she was used to squatting higher
so now she's learning how to squat rock
bottom and go deep uh here's Sammy 125
lbs on the squat and I just was getting
a feel for what she could do I didn't
really know what to expect I like her
wide stance because she can't go real
deep uh because of her hip flexion
Mobility I suspect she's got you know a
hip Anatomy that isn't well suited for
deep squats but it's kind of like I kept
loading up weight and being surprised
that she could do it that was 135 I
thought it looked pretty good and here's
Aaron with 95lb squat I was I always
remind her to keep those knees out uh
some sometimes she tends to Cave good
and uh form looks amazing she's such a
awesome deep squatter keeps good uh back
position just excellent form here this
was a rep max that's what we were going
for here she got 95 for five which is
almost her body weight she weighs like
98 right now um she's weighed 98 lbs for
like the last few years okay here's Sam
a 175 and that still kind of looked easy
she needs to learn to be more stable
which comes in time but keep in mind
this is her first time ever squatting
heavy with a barbell so she's a freak of
nature I had her do it again and uh got
175 I kept it there uh just to see uh
for a first session what we do over time
and this is also Sam's first time doing
heavy barbell devadas with
me try it once last year she used a
heavy kable I have a 203 lb kable and
she could get that for like 15 reps by
the end after 6 months of with me and uh
ready but she never really did one time
we tried to do barbell deadlifts and her
form was horrendous so I stopped her
because I trained six girls at once with
the glute Squad but now I have more time
to devote to her oneon-one
um and so I was extremely happy with her
deadlift form here this is 155 it looked
good she rounds slightly at the low back
but not too much uh for my liking I'm
okay with it she uses good leg Drive uh
here's Aaron learning bench she does
tend
to be asymmetrical her right her left
side tends to be higher than her right
side so I have to remind her about that
but she was benching like a bodybuilder
this is only her fourth time bench
pressing in like the last year she
hasn't been doing any bench pressing and
she was benching like a bodybuilder cuz
she's a bikini competitor she learned to
do like a wide stance and and lowering
it up higher on her chest so now trying
to teach her how to bench like a
powerlifter and as you know that's not
not easy to transition from here's Sammy
185 lb deadlift uh excellent form
here um and Sammy uses her glutes well
all the way through some people don't
use their glutes well to lock out the
deadlift okay here's Aaron benching
again 65 lbs I wanted to do three sets
with this I think she gets six reps the
first set five reps the second set and
four reps the third set but again I'm
very happy with her form because she
just learned this her fourth session
back she's got good discipline there
form looked good over time she'll learn
to be more tight okay here's Sammy I
told her I wanted to try a 225lb
deadlift and she said no way that she
can do it and she did it twice you can
see her trying not to smile because
she's so excited that she did it and how
how amazed at how strong she is so um
Sammy is a freak of nature here's Aaron
here again 65 lb bench press I love the
form
good lowering the bar to a good position
the the arm angle looks great uh pausing
for a split second there
so very proud of Aaron's bench press
form there uh here's Aaron doing hip
thrust this 135
lbs uh over time Aaron will learn to get
her feet in proper position right when
she starts you do see her shift her feet
as the set goes on trying to find a
better placement that's common in time
she has not been hip thrusting me very
long with me very long uh over time
she'll learn to come lower now here's
Sammy I'm just teaching her bench press
for the first time it's hard to teach
someone while you're also filming but
this is just the barn I'm telling her I
I made her go narrower grip with than
she's used to I made her lower it down
lower on her chest you don't need keep
her elbows more tucked and for just
learning it for the first time this is
amazing uh Aaron with 185 lb hip thrust
uh great
form perfect Shin angle there holds it
for a pause I'd like her to go slightly
higher at lock out just a couple inches
but I'm still happy with that okay
here's Sammy with a 65lb bench press
very happy with this form considering
the the legs look good the keeping an
arch in the back the arm angle
kind of pausing at the chest I'm very
very happy with this form considering
it's sometimes so hard to teach people
powerlifting bench press form when
they've all they've done is bench
pressing form here's 85 you know I'm
trying to take a picture for Instagram I
should have probably been behind the bar
but I thought Sammy would be able to get
this with ease anyway I'll rush over
because she lined up too close to the
racks she hits the rack on the way down
so she's not quite symmetrical but
anyway learning experience I showed her
how she needs to line up further away
from the rack so she doesn't hit so it's
a classic mistake there okay here's a
225b hip thrust with Aaron very good
form uh shifting her feet around a
little bit but looks great squeezing
that end range Aaron's awesome this is
2.25 times body weight for her and now
here's Sammy doing a last set of 65b
bench press she's a little fatigued
she looks to the looks to the side a
little bit I always tell my lifters to
look straight ahead a lot of them want
to look side to side she's not quite
that stable but keep in mind this is her
first session with me learning bench
press so super happy with this uh little
wobbly but she'll get much better in
time um next set we've got Aaron doing a
oh we recorded very late on this this
was another set of 225 lb hip thrust and
then here here's Aaron doing a set of
band seated hip
abductions this is an awesome exercise
for Aaron in fact when I palpate Aaron's
glutes when she does these she gets more
tension in her glutes her upper and
lower glutes with these than just about
anything this is one of her best glute
exercises it's not for doesn't do the
same with everyone but with Aaron this
is just an amazing exercise for her so
she's doing tons of these each session
she does a couple sets here's Sammy
doing 225lb hip thrust uh in the past
she always did these with me handing the
bar to her so she got spoiled so it's
kind of awkward for her to learn how to
do it from the ground up cuz I would set
the bar on her lap and she didn't think
she could do these cuz she's just been
doing 185lb hip thrust at her house good
and I made her do 225 and she got it
just fine she got it 10 rips and then I
went up to 275 and she gets it Sammy has
crazy end range hip extension strength
she always goes up all the way and and
uh it's amazing she I don't have to tell
her to go high lock it out she's got the
densest glutes out of anyone I've ever
trained um glutes are Rock Solid not the
biggest glutes but the densest um here's
her doing 275 again she's a little bit
asymmetrical in that one side will
bounce before the other over time you
gain coordination you tend to be more
symmetrical um but then she pauses at
the top for a 10sec ISO hold or 5C
whatever and then uh here's Sammy
finishing off I think I had her do two
sets of this but I only recorded one
this is band seated hip abduction
abductions this was too easy for her
next time we'll go heavier uh she ended
up doing 30 reps and uh go high she's
laughing there because it's very awkward
to be filmed while doing these um but
this a great exercise to throw in at the
end because it just gives you more uh
metabolic stress in the glutes um but
it's not hard on the body it doesn't the
nervous system you can do these you know
five times a week and it doesn't it's
not taxing on you it doesn't induce too
much faue it doesn't wear you out okay
and it gets a crazy burn so I always do
this and then Sam uh I had Sammy do a a
set of chinups just to see if she could
do it cuz she hasn't done any upper body
in so long and she busts out three
perfect chin-ups here which was amazing
Aaron Aaron does uh some upper body
stuff on her own but Samy's just going
to be doing with me so I had her do that
but anyway I hope you like the video
thank you very much for watching